Guide to the Stanford University Architectural Collection SC1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Architectural drawings
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 1962 Sep 20; 04-250 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Marcum
    Description: High Energy Physics Lab Proposed East End Station
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 1966-03-09; 04-250, 04-900T (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Spencer, Lee and Busse
    Description: Modernization of the High Energy Physics Lab--Struc Eng: Pregnoff and Matheu. Elec/Mech Eng: Broback and Associates
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 1966 Mar 9; 04-250, 04-900T (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Proposed High Energy Physics Lab Expansion (formerly Building 270)
  - Cecil H. Green Library, East Wing, 1999; 03-210 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: holey associates
    Description: Information Center, furniture plan
  - Education (Cubberly), 03-300 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Education Building - Basement Plan
    Format: negative film
  - Education (Cubberley), 9/26 - 10/3/79; 03-300 (Box B1)
    Artist: TDR
    Description: Floor plans for first, second and third floors - based on 8/31/36 drawings by Bakewell and Brown; revised by TDR in 1979
  - Meyer Library, 1960 Dec 15; 03-400 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Stanford Undergraduate Library
    Format: drawing
  - Meyer Library, 1964; 03-400 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Architectural (26), site draining (2), and landscape plans (7)
    # of Drawings: 35
  - Meyer Library, 1966; 03-400 (Box C1)
    Description: Undergraduate Library: Proposed double-tiered stack layout. Basement floor plan.--
  - Meyer Library, 1964-10-01; 03-400 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Meyer Memorial Library Basement Stacks Floor Plan; Landscape Arch: Thomas D. Church and Associates--Mech/Elec Eng: G.L. Gendler and Associates
  - Meyer Library, 1964, 1966; 03-400 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Music Listening Facilities plans and diagrams
    Format: diazo prints
  - Meyer Library, circa 1970; 03-400 (Box A1)
    Description: Meyer Undergraduate Library Floorplans. Possibly produced by the Library.
    Format: printed
  - Meyer Library, 03-400 (Box C1)
    Description: Meyer Library sketch of exterior.
    Format: reproduction (negative)
  - Meyer Library, 03-400 (Box B1)
    Description: Meyer Library. Artist’s rendering of exterior. Original drawing (ink and colored pencil) and b/w photographic reproduction.
    Format: 1 drawing, 1 photograph
  - Meyer Library, 03-400 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Meyer Library Floor Plans--Landscape Arch: Thomas D. Church and Associates--Mech/Elec Eng: G.L. Gendler and Associates
  - Hoover Library Group, 1930; 03-xxx (Box C1)
    Description: Proposed Food Research, War Memorial, and Hoover Library Group
    Format: 4 blueprints, 2 tissues
  - Stanford University Inn, circa 1898; 03-xxx (Box A1)
    Description: Stanford University Inn; rendering of exterior, front view
  - Parking Lot B Jordan Quad, 1964 Mar 17; 04-000 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Nelson, Oscar F. Jr.
    Description: Schematic for Parking Lot B - Jordan Quad--(stored as Q4 but could also be Q14)
  - Physics and Jordan Quads, 1962 Sep 10; 04-000 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Plan of Circulation and Building Sites in Physics and Jordan Quads--(stored as Q4 but could also be Q14)
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 1953-07-15; 04-200, 04-250 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Spencer and Ambrose
    Description: Perspective Science Quad Plan - Microwave Laboratory--Assoc. Arch: W.A. Talley and Alton Lee
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 1963; 04-250 (Box C1)
    Description: High Energy Physics Lab
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 04-250 (Box map case Na16)
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 04-250, 04-900T (Box map case Na16)
    Description: High Energy Physics Laboratory (formerly Building 270)
  - Ginzton Labs, High Energy Physics Lab, 1966 Jul 1; 04-250, 04-900T (Box map case Na16)
    Description: High Energy Physics Laboratory Expansion (formerly Building 270)
  - Electronics Research Lab, Applied Electronics Lab (SEL), 1960 Oct 1; 04-300 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Proposed Double-Decking Electronics Research Lab
  - Electronics Research Lab, Applied Electronics Lab (SEL), 1956 Dec 5; 04-300, 04-350 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Ambrose and Spencer
    Description: Applied Electronis Laboratory (Electronics Research Lab)
  - Electronics Research Lab, Applied Electronics Lab (SEL), 1956 Feb 21; 04-300, 04-350 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: First and Second Floor Plans, Roof Plans - Applied Electronics Lab
  - Henry Salvatori Geophysics Lab, 1953-06; 04-400 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Henry Salvatori Geophysics Lab
  - McCullough Building, Physics Lecture Hall, 1958-02; 04-500 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Dailey, Garner A.
    Description: Proposed Science Quadrangle Development--(covers 04-490, 04-500, 04-520; stored as 04-500)
  - McCullough Building, Physics Lecture Hall, 04-500 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Dailey, Gardner A.
    Description: Proposed Quadrangle Development (Physics especially)
  - McCullough Building, Physics Lecture Hall, 1961-05-29; 04-500 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: JFM
    Description: Proposed Quadrangle Development (Physics)
  - McCullough Building, Physics Lecture Hall, 04-500 (Box C1)
    Description: Proposed Physics Lecture Hall. Artist’s rendering of exterior.
    Format: graphite and colored pencil on paper, mounted on board
  - Varian Physics Lab, 1966 Jan 16; 04-520 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Varian Basement Addition: Site Location
  - Earth Sciences, 1965 Aug 31; 04-600 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Alterations to Earth Sciences Laboratories; razed 1975
  - High Tension Lab, 04-600 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: High Tension Laboratory - Electrical Engineering--(razed 1975)
  - Roble Gym, 1915; 04-650 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Women’s Bath house and Swimming Tank for LSJU revisions
    Format: original drawings and blueprints
  - Roble Gym, 1979; 04-650 (Box not specified)
    Artist: J. Pollard
    Description: See Print P312 for watercolor renderings of furnishings 1979
    Format: original watercolors
  - Terman Engineering Center, 1974 Oct 9; 04-700 (Box map case Na16)
    Architect: Weese, J. and Weese, H. and Assoc.
    Description: Terman Engineering Center--Elec Eng: Mel Camisa; Mech Eng: Kasin, Guttman and Assoc--Struc Eng: Nishkian, Hammel and Assoc.
    Negative
  - Terman Engineering Center, 1974; 04-700 (Box B1)
    Description: Terman Engineering Center site plan showing building, pond, landscaping
    Format: negative stat (for printing)
  - Terman Engineering Center, 04-700 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Sketch of Terman Engineering Center
    Format: Sketch
  - Terman Engineering Center Library, 1975; 04-700 (Box D1)
    Description: Site plans, floor plans, mechanicals, etc.
    # of Drawings: 25
  - Temporary Telephone Facility, Apr-70; 04-910T (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Site Location for Temporary Telephone Facility
  - Temporary Telephone Facility, May-72; 04-910T (Box map case Na16)
  - Dendral Modular Building, 1973 Dec 15; 04-920T (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Proposed Relocation of the Dendral Modular building--(moved to 14-905T, 1982)
  - Hansen Labs Electroplating Facility, 1971 Oct 18; 04-950 (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Proposed New Liquid Nitrogen Cryogenic Tank - W.W. Hansen Labs of Physics (includes site plan)
  - Hansen Labs Electroplating Facility, 04-950T (Box map case Na16)
    Description: Hansen labs physics
  - Lomita Mall, 1966; 04-xxx (Box A1)
    Architect: Church, Thomas D. and Assoc.
    Description: Lomita Mall Schematic Landscape Plan--(stored as Q4 but could also be Q1)
    Format: photo-reproduction
  - Parking Lot G, 05-000 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Conceptual Schematic - Parking Lot “G”
  - [Lake Lagunita], 1959 Mar 10; 05-000 (Box map case Na17)
    Architect: S. U. Planning Office
    Description: Study of Lagunita Improvements. “Approved in principal by the Adv. Comm. on Land and Building Development 10 March 1959”; shows new campus drive and foothill rd; changes to shoreline
    Format: colored pencil on papers
  - Lagunita, 05-010 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Lagunita Court laundry dryers
  - Roble Hall, 1917; 05-100 (Box not specified)
    Architect: Geo. W. Kelham; Hunter and Hudson engineers
    Description: Plumbing plans for women's dormitory
    Format: blueprints (brittle, one damaged)
  - Florence Moore Hall, 1955; 05-200 (Box B2)
    Description: Photo of model
    Format: photograph
  - Florence Moore Hall, 05-200 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Photo of preliminary study and proposal
    Format: Photo
  - Knoll, 05-300 (Box map case Na17)
    Architect: Mullgardt, Louis G.
    Description: Blueprints - wiring and plumbing plans
    Format: Blueprints
  - Knoll, 1942; 05-300 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: President’s residence - Stanford 1942 - mostly landscaping information
    Format: encapsulated
  - Knoll, undated; 05-300 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Block Plan, showing roads, lawns, orchard, etc.
  - Knoll, 1917 May 2; 05-300 (Box map case Na17)
    Architect: Mullgardt, Louis G.; Brunnier, H.J. engineer
    Description: Third story walls - roof plan and chimneys
  - Theta Delta Chi, 05-410 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University Undergraduate housing - 4 subunits;--Includes 05-410, 05-440 (Sigma Alpha Epsilon), and 05-450 (Kappa Sigma)
  - Theta Delta Chi, 05-410 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University undergraduate housing: Kappa Sigma Unit #4, Theta Delta Chi #2, SAE #3
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 05-440 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University Undergraduate housing - 4 subunits;--Includes 05-410 (Theta Delta Chi), 05-440, and 05-450 (Kappa Sigma)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 05-440 (Box map case Na17)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 05-440 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University undergraduate housing group #1 (inc. SAE)
  - Kappa Sigma, 05-450 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University Undergraduate housing - 4 subunits;--Includes 05-410 (Theta Delta Chi), 05-440 (Sigma Alpha Epsilon), and 05-450
  - Kappa Sigma, 05-450 (Box map case Na17)
  - Lambda Nu, 05-520 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University undergraduate housing group 2 [incl. 05-530 and 05-550]
  - Lambda Nu, 05-520 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Undergraduate Fraternity Housing - second group (incl. 05-530 and 05-550)
  - Kappa Alpha, 05-530 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University undergraduate housing group 2 [incl. 05-520 and 05-550]
  - Kappa Alpha, 05-530 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Undergraduate Fraternity Housing - second group (incl. 05-520 and 05-550)
  - Kappa Alpha, 05-530 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University Undergraduate Housing Group #2 and Kappa Alpha - Study of typical fraternity housing cluster #2
  - 353 Campus Drive, 05-550 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Stanford University undergraduate housing group 2 [incl. 05-520 and 05-530]
  - 353 Campus Drive, 05-550 (Box map case Na17)
    Description: Undergraduate Fraternity Housing - second group (incl. 05-520 and 05-530)
  - Encina Hall, circa 1891; 06-010 (Box B2)
    Architect: Shepley, Rutan, and Coolidge
    Description: Leland Stanford Junior University Large Dormitory No. 1. Elevations and sections. [Encina Hall Center and South Wings]
    Format: possibly microfilm reproductions
  - Encina Hall, 1958-59; 06-010 (Box B2)
    Architect: Weihe, Frick and Kruse
    Description: Remodeling of Encina Hall, 1958-59.--Incomplete set; labeled “not as-builts”
    Format: film negs of blueprints
    # of Drawings: 36
  - Encina Hall, 1997; 06-010 (Box D1)
    Artist: Zeman
    Description: Watercolor sketch of new meeting room in Encina Hall (the original dining hall); part of the remodeling of Encina to house the Institute for International Studies
    Format: watercolor sketch
  - Encina Hall, 1992 ?; 06-010 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Drawings for the Institute for International Studies and boards containing illustrations of furniture and samples of materials.
    # of Drawings: 200
  - Encina Hall, circa 1891; 06-010 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Leland Stanford Junior University Large Dormitory No. 2. Front elevation (Encina Hall)
  - Encina Hall, 1989 Dec 6; 06-010 (Box Basement MC)
    Architect: Hoover Associates
    Description: East and West Wings - power outlet plan and Componentry/furniture plan. Central Area - Componentry/furniture plan.
  - Encina Hall, 1989 Oct 20; 06-010 (Box Basement MC)
  - Encina Hall, 1997; 06-010 (Box Basement MC)
    Architect: Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Assoc.
    Description: Instittute for International Studies Encina Hall Central/ South Floor Plans (ground, first and second)
  - Encina Hall, 1997; 06-030 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Instittute for International Studies Encina Hall Central/ South Set of 10 plans - general notes, details, floor plans
  - Encina Hall, 1997; 06-030 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Instittute for International Studies Encina Hall Central/ South Set of 14 plans
    # of Drawings: 14
  - Encina Hall, 1997; 06-030 (Box Basement MC)
  - Encina Hall, 1997; 06-030 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Instittute for International Studies Encina Hall Central/ South Set of 12 plans - electrical
  - Food Research Institute, 06-020 (Box not specified)
    Description: see drawings stored under 03-100 and 03-120
  - Food Research Institute, 06-020 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Preliminary Sketch for Proposed Food Administration and Hoover Library Building [focus is on FRI]
  - Encina Hall (East), circa 1997; 06-030 (Box D1)
    Description: Encina Hall East Stanford University. Support. Includes floor plan (floor not specified) and examples of paint colors and types of surfaces.
    Format: multi, mounted on foamcore
  - Encina Hall (East) Parking, 1965-08-19; 06-030 parking (Box A1)
    Artist: j.b.
    Description: A Plan for revisions to parking at east side of Encina Hall
  - Eating Clubs Parking Lot, 06-050 parking (Box A1)
    Description: Eating clubs parking lot
  - Branner-Toyon Quadrangle, 1962; 06-100, 06-200 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: View from Escondido towards Hoover Tower, perspective
    Format: hand-colored
  - Branner-Toyon Quadrangle, 1962; 06-100, 06-200 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: East and West Elevations
  - Branner-Toyon Quadrangle, 1962; 06-100, 06-200 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: View from the green west, towards Branner and Toyon Halls, perspective
  - Toyon Hall, 1922; 06-200 (Box C2)
    Description: Set of 35 drawings
    Format: blueprint copies, possibly from microfilm
  - Toyon Hall, 1922; 06-200 (Box C2)
    Description: Residence Hall #3 (Toyon). Paper copies from microfiche or film (marked with “Mark Larwood Company”)
    # of Drawings: 15
  - Crothers Memorial Hall, 1954-05; 06-300 (Box A1)
    Description: Crothers Memorial
    Format: photo of sketch
  - Crothers Memorial Hall, 1946 Aug 21; 06-300, 06-350 (Box B2)
    Description: Crothers Dormitory Summary, Sheet 2. Illustrates various layouts of rooms.
    Format: negative photostat mounted on board
  - Crothers Memorial Hall, 1954-05; 06-350 (Box C2)
    Description: Crothers Memorial Stanford University. Artist’s rendering of exterior.
    Format: negative copy
  - Crothers Memorial Hall, 06-350 (Box A1)
    Description: Crothers Hall - artist’s rendering of exterior
  - Crothers Memorial Hall, 1946; 06-350 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Preliminary - Crothers Hall
  - Crothers Memorial Hall, 06-350 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Crothers Hall
    Format: sketch on tissue
  - Stern Hall, 06-500 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Stern Hall Addition - site plan and area development, bedroom and toilet room plans
  - Stern Hall, 06-500 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Faculty Residence Stern hall
  - Stern Hall, 06-500 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Preliminary for Lucie B. Stern Residential Hall for Men
  - Stern Hall, 06-500 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Study for Dormitories - Stanford (Stern), Schemes 1, 2, and 4
  - Stern Hall, 06-500 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Stern addition and proposals
    Format: photolike
  - Stern Hall, 1962-05-14; 06-500 (Box A1)
    Architect: Sands, Maurice
    Description: Lucy Stern Room Floor Plan [same room as Larkin Lounge ?]
  - Stern Hall, 1961 Dec 15; 06-500 (Box A1)
    Description: Stern Hall Larkin lounge - artist’s rendering of furniture arrangement
  - Museum, 1907 (approx); 07-100 (Box D1)
    Description: Lower floor plan of addition to Leland Stanford Junr. Museum; includes notes in red pencil re post-quake reconstruction
  - Museum, 1902-12-04; 07-100 (Box map case Na19)
    Architect: G. McB and Co.
    Description: Stanford University Museum - Schedule drawing and setters diagrams for rotundas of additions to the LSJ Museum
    Format: blueprint, encapsulated
  - Museum, 1905-07-22; 07-100 (Box B2)
    Architect: Gladding McBean and Co.
    Description: Stanford University Museum terra cotta bases in rotundas, 1st story.
    Format: blueprints, encapsulated
  - Museum, 2005-08-27; 07-100 (Box B2)
    Description: Seating plan - front of Stanford Museum [performance not specified]
  - Museum, 07-100 (Box map case Na19)
    Architect: Frederick H. Meyer
    Description: Restoration of North Wing LSJ Museum
  - Old Chemistry, 1976-05-26; 07-200 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Swain chemistry library expansion
  - Museum, 1913; 07-100 (Box SAL)
    Description: Reconstruction plans - museum--[rolled in tube and stored at SAL]
  - Museum, 1916-09-05; 07-100 (Box B2)
    Architect: G. M. H.
    Description: Fumigator for Leland Stanford Jr. Museum 9-5-16
  - Museum, 1958 Aug 1; 07-100 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Preliminary study for landscaping and parking between Museum and Anatomy-Bacteriology building
  - Museum, 07-100 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Remodelling - Art Museum
  - Manzanita Park, 06-600 (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Temporary student housing in mobile homes--116 trailers
  - Men's Gymnasium (original), 1912 Feb 8; 06-xxx (Box D1)
    Architect: Keefer, C. T.
    Description: Proposed Changes in L.S.J.U. Gymnasium
  - Proposed chemistry building, 1973 Nov 8; 07-000 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Site Location Study. Proposed chemistry building. [same basic location as current Mudd Building]
  - Old Chemistry, 1907-03; 07-200 (Box C2)
    Artist: V.R.G., approved by C.B. Wing
    Description: Detail of front gable of chemistry building
    Format: photocopy
  - Old Chemistry, 1904 Feb 13; 07-200 (Box B2)
    Architect: Granis, J.G., and Co (engineers)
    Description: Ventilation of chemical building includes typical section on line “A” “A” and quantitative and qualitative labs system of ceiling vents - Physical Chemistry
  - Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry Building, 07-210 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry Building asphalt paving revision
  - Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry Building, 07-210 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: View of sunken court, Stanford University - chemistry new facilities
  - Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry Building, Organic Chemistry Building, 07-210, 07-250 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: View from Lomita Drive, Stanford University - chemistry new facilities
  - Chemistry Conference, Chemical Engineering Conference, 07-240, 07-280 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Proposed seminar building Stanford University chemistry group (Chemistry Gazebo)
  - Organic Chemistry Research Building, 07-250 (Box B2)
    Architect: Clark, Stromquist, Potter and Ehrlich
    Description: Organic Chemistry Research Building view from northeast. Artist’s rendering.
    Format: photo reproduction
  - Organic Chemistry Research Building, 07-250 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Organic chemistry research building
  - Organic Chemistry Research Building, 07-250 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Organic research lab
  - Stauffer Chemistry Buildings, 07-260, 07-270, 07-290 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Proposed Chemistry Group, elevations
  - Stauffer Chemistry Buildings, 07-270 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Physical Chemistry Laboratory completion
  - Stauffer Chemistry Buildings, 1-Aug-50; 07-290 (Box C2)
    Architect: Paxton, R.R.
    Description: Stanford University Proposed Chemical Engineering Building. Floor plan
    Format: ink on linen
  - Herrin Laboratories, 6-Jul-62; 07-400 (Box A1)
    Architect: Pfleuger, Milton T.
    Description: Biology court, artist’s rendering
    Format: reproduction of pencil sketch
  - Herrin Laboratories, 07-400 (Box A1)
    Architect: [Pfleuger, Milton T.]
    Artist: Kruger
    Description: Biology building, artist’s rendering of exterior
    Format: photograph of sketch
  - Herrin Laboratories, 07-400, 07-450 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Biology Court - schematic plans
  - Biology Hall, 1967; 07-410 (Box map case Na19)
    Architect: Pflueger, Milton
    Description: South centrance to teaching wing - Center for Biological Sciences, Stanford
  - Center for Biological Sciences, 1967; 07-410 (Box cage)
    Description: 1. 3rd floor research wing #A-7--2. ground floor teaching wing #A-9
  - Sherman Fairchild Science Building, 07-520 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Sherman Fairchild Center
  - Louis B. Mayer Cancer Bio. Research Lab, 07-550 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Governor’s Lane Complex - elevations
    Format: elevations
  - Psychiatric Clinic Building, 07-920 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Psychiatry Clinic Building for Stanford Univ. Medical Center
  - Encina Gymnasium, 08-010 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Encina Gym pools
  - Encina Gymnasium, 08-010 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: First floor plan of Encina Gym, undated. Paper copy of os original on 2 sheets
  - Old Pavilion, 08-200 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Addition to Basketball Pavilion - Stanford
  - Tanner Fountain, 08-320 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Tanner Fountain - Stanford University
  - Graduate School of Business, 08-350 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Graduate School of Business
  - Galvez House, Galvez House Annex, 08-500, 08-520 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Galvez House schemes A-D
  - Frost Amphitheatre, 08-600 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Proposed orchestra pit for Laurence Frost Amphitheatre
  - Frost Amphitheatre, 08-600 (Box rolled)
    Description: Frost Amphitheatre
  - Frost Amphitheatre, 1937; 08-600 (Box C2)
    Description: Laurence Frost Memorial Amphitheatre at Stanford University. Designed by A. E. Roth. Surveyed and drawn by J. G. Rawhauser. 1936-37. Includes a key to trees
    Format: copy
  - Frost Amphitheatre, 1937; 08-600 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Laurence Frost Memorial Amphitheatre at Stanford University. Comptroller A. E. Roth. Surveyed and drawn by J. G. Rawhauser. 1936-37. Includes a key to trees
  - Encina Hall parking, 5-Nov-59; 08-xxx (Box C2)
    Description: Study of additional parking for Encina Hall, on Arguello Street next to Basketball Pavilion
  - 315 Bonair Siding, 09-100 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Bonair Siding site study
  - Stanford Federal Credit Union, 09-120 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Credit Union - site study
  - Fire and Police Facility, 09-200 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Proposed Site Expansion - fire and police building - site plan
  - Maples Pavilion, 09-300 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Athletic Pavilion (Maples) site plan